<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>painting on ミルミント</title>
    <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/tags/painting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in painting on ミルミント</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/tags/painting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer House in the Azores</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-28-summer-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-28-summer-house/</guid>
      <description>The Azores had been a possession of Vekllei since 2002, when they were leased from Portugal indefinitely. The lease was defunct by the time of Vekllei’s independence from U.K. occupation in 2015, and the new state took formal ownership over the small Atlantic islands.
The Azores was Vekllei’s resort region, often called simply the “holiday isles”. Brief reprieves from the North Atlantic cold were granted to hundreds of thousands domestic tourists each year in resorts and holiday rentals alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Base Camp</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-21-base-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-21-base-camp/</guid>
      <description>Just a paint-sketch.
The puffin scouts set up camp not far from the rest, just outside of Krafla in the Lava region. When they moved south tomorrow, thick native grasses and trees would give way to flower-tundras and bare hills, and by Tuesday they’d be in the heart of Lava — empty and extraterrestrial and volcanic.
The Krafla high-energy communications tower was visible from all over the region. It provided uninterrupted radio to most of North Lava, and could relay signals through satellites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canal Living</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-03-canal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-03-canal/</guid>
      <description>Atlantic Salmon was the best in the world, and Vekllei had a lot of it. Ocean-going fishing boats brought their haul to Ro, where they cruised wide postwar canals and unloaded tonnes of shiny, bright salmon into processing plants. If a new factory was built, so too was a canal or a railroad. Nothing was trucked. Fish was traded fresh in markets or turned into emulsifiers and fertiliser.
The canals were worked heavily, and few fishing vessels were incorporated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>