<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zelda on ミルミント</title>
    <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/tags/zelda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zelda on ミルミント</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 05:22:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/tags/zelda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The 31st Century — Vekllei throughout our Solar System</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-08-09-spaceship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 05:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-08-09-spaceship/</guid>
      <description>The Epoch of Rest We’ve spent a lot of time in the 21st century — but Tzipora is biologically immortal. Where does she go from here? Well, let’s enjoy a small glimpse at that future together, by winding the clock forward one thousand years.
By 3076, our Solar System is a pleasant place to be. Most of the planets we once gazed at from afar are now habitable and lived on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Tzipora — concept panel for a Vekllei comic</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-08-01-tzipora-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 06:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-08-01-tzipora-concept/</guid>
      <description>Unique among girls There are a lot of things Tzipora does differently to everybody else, and they start to make a lot more sense when you realise Tzipora either does not realise she is unusual, or does not care.
She has a lot of endearing characteristics that give great character to her mannerisms and physicality. She has a small overbite that makes her look a little froggy, and ritually pulls on her shirt and wipes her nose in anxious conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer House in the Azores</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-28-summer-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-28-summer-house/</guid>
      <description>The Azores had been a possession of Vekllei since 2002, when they were leased from Portugal indefinitely. The lease was defunct by the time of Vekllei’s independence from U.K. occupation in 2015, and the new state took formal ownership over the small Atlantic islands.
The Azores was Vekllei’s resort region, often called simply the “holiday isles”. Brief reprieves from the North Atlantic cold were granted to hundreds of thousands domestic tourists each year in resorts and holiday rentals alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Base Camp</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-21-base-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-21-base-camp/</guid>
      <description>Just a paint-sketch.
The puffin scouts set up camp not far from the rest, just outside of Krafla in the Lava region. When they moved south tomorrow, thick native grasses and trees would give way to flower-tundras and bare hills, and by Tuesday they’d be in the heart of Lava — empty and extraterrestrial and volcanic.
The Krafla high-energy communications tower was visible from all over the region. It provided uninterrupted radio to most of North Lava, and could relay signals through satellites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tzipora’s ‘Every Day Carry’</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-20-edc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 05:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-20-edc/</guid>
      <description>Like a lot of girls of poverty, Tzipora was very possessive of her things. No food was ever left on her plate. There was a deep anxiety that whatever wasn’t claimed would be lost.
She was also naturally obsessive and material-oriented, keenly aware of the importance of objects measured by metrics in her own silly head. You can discover a lot about a person from their trinkets and toys — let’s discover a bit about Tzipora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Race for Inefficiency — Vekllei’s advocation of austerity, apathy, and playfulness as economic principles</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-13-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 04:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-07-13-economy/</guid>
      <description>This post is about the economy of Vekllei. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a long one. If you have any questions, just ask.
Overview of the Bureau System There are many thousands of companies busy with work in Vekllei. The vast majority of these companies are single-person shops (S.p.A., or senrouiva pettetie anaproiouya). Also common are wobbly shops, or co-operative businesses (S.q.A., or senrouiva qualitie anaproiouya). The largest of the non-bureau companies are village factories (S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vekllei Crown — coins of a moneyless country</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-24-crown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 05:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-24-crown/</guid>
      <description>Vekllei, legendarily, does not use circulate currency. Goods and services are moved and offered arbitrarily, provided amply in abundance. Anything that is not abundant is manufactured and distributed directly under the control of a bureau, which is a trade organ responsible to the affairs of the country. At no point do coins or paper currency change hands in the day-to-day affairs of the country.
In this sense, Vekllei is usually described as “moneyless” — yet it does in fact have a currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Most Beautiful Woman</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-12-ayn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 03:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-12-ayn/</guid>
      <description>When Tzipora first laid eyes on Ayn, hours after her arrival in the country, she thought, “that’s the most beautiful woman I’ve ever seen.”
It wasn’t just her features or figure that captured Tzipora’s attention — it was also her confident, inconspicuous movements and a quiet self-assuredness that seemed obvious in her gentle expression and posture. Tzipora was not quite sure how to describe it. Her beauty was very alive in the way she inhabited a space, as she walked into the hotel lounge to meet them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canal Living</title>
      <link>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-03-canal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://millmint.studio/newsroom/blog/posts/2020-06-03-canal/</guid>
      <description>Atlantic Salmon was the best in the world, and Vekllei had a lot of it. Ocean-going fishing boats brought their haul to Ro, where they cruised wide postwar canals and unloaded tonnes of shiny, bright salmon into processing plants. If a new factory was built, so too was a canal or a railroad. Nothing was trucked. Fish was traded fresh in markets or turned into emulsifiers and fertiliser.
The canals were worked heavily, and few fishing vessels were incorporated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>